#### Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/my-nguyen-a52324171 (LinkedIn) minnie-ng.webflow.io/ (Portfolio)

### Top Skills

Figma (Software) Design Principles Wireframing

# My Nguyen

Senior UI/UX Designer at NEC Vietnam

Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

# Summary

My name is My Nguyen.

I'm a UI/UX Designer and with:

More than 3 years of UX/UI Mobile product design experience.

Sometimes I also do Web/Software design.

Someone who is studious, detail-oriented and observed and work well independently.

Bachelor of Graphic Arts (B.A.) degree in Asia University of Arts.

# Experience

NEC Vietnam
Senior UI/UX Designer
May 2023 - Present (1 year 11 months)
Vietnam

Digitoy.XYZ Technology JSC UI/UX Designer March 2019 - March 2023 (4 years 1 month) Vietnam

#### Education

Asia University of Arts and Designer (2014 - 2018)